Office of the Associate Vice-President, Academic fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Academic support departments - correspondence, 1983 - 1998; F-201-3; 4.92 m of textual records; Physical description: includes 16 oversize architectural plans (see sub-sub-series 2 and 11).
  - Associate Vice-President, Academic, 1983 - 1998; F-201-3-2; 2.57 m of textual records and other material; Physical description: includes 11 oversize architectural plans (sub-sub-series 2).
    - Associate Vice-President, Academic - general, 1983 - 1998; F-201-3-2-1; 1.09 m of textual records
      - Western Universities Telecourse Consortium, 1994; F-201-3-2-1-48 (Archival box - standard 201-69)
      - General correspondence, 1995; F-201-3-2-1-49 (Archival box - standard 201-28)
      - AVPA - general, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-201-3-2-1-50 (Archival box - standard 201-28)
      - AVPA - general, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-201-3-2-1-51 (Archival box - standard 201-28)
      - Draft policy - conflict of interest, 1996; F-201-3-2-1-52 (Archival box - standard 201-29)
      - General correspondence, vol. 1, 1996; F-201-3-2-1-53 (Archival box - standard 201-29)
      - General correspondence, vol. 2, 1996; F-201-3-2-1-54 (Archival box - standard 201-29)
      - General correspondence, vol. 3, 1996; F-201-3-2-1-55 (Archival box - standard 201-69)
      - S. Roppel - correspondence, vol. 1, 1996; F-201-3-2-1-56 (Archival box - standard 201-29)
      - S. Roppel - correspondence, vol. 2, 1996; F-201-3-2-1-57 (Archival box - standard 201-29)
      - The Univeristies Presidents Council of BC (TUPC), 1996; F-201-3-2-1-58 (Archival box - standard 201-29)
      - General correspondence, vol. 1, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-1-59 (Archival box - standard 201-29)
      - General correspondence, vol. 2, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-1-60 (Archival box - standard 201-30)
      - General correspondence, vol. 3, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-1-61 (Archival box - standard 201-30)
      - General correspondence, vol. 4, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-1-62 (Archival box - standard 201-30)
      - General correspondence, vol. 5, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-1-63 (Archival box - standard 201-30)
      - General correspondence, vol. 1, 1998; F-201-3-2-1-64 (Archival box - standard 201-30)
      - General correspondence, vol. 2, 1998; F-201-3-2-1-65 (Archival box - standard 201-30)
      - General correspondence, vol. 3, 1998; F-201-3-2-1-66 (Archival box - standard 201-31)
      - General correspondence, vol. 4, 1998; F-201-3-2-1-67 (Archival box - standard 201-31)
      - General correspondence, vol. 5, 1998; F-201-3-2-1-68 (Archival box - standard 201-31)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, vol. 1, 1998; F-201-3-2-1-69 (Archival box - standard 201-31)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, vol. 2, 1998; F-201-3-2-1-70 (Archival box - standard 201-31)
      - Residence death, 1994; F-201-3-2-1-71 (Archival box - standard 201-28)
    - Space, 1985 - 1997; F-201-3-2-2; 53 cm of textual records
      University Space Advisory Committee
      - Space, vol. 1, 1986 - 1989; F-201-3-2-2-1 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.a.
      - Space, vol. 2, 1986 - 1989; F-201-3-2-2-2 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
      - Space, vol. 3, 1986 - 1989; F-201-3-2-2-3 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
      - Space, vol. 4, 1986 - 1989; F-201-3-2-2-4 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
      - Renovations, vol. 1, 1986 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-5 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.b.
      - Renovations, vol. 2, 1986 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-6 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
      - Renovations, vol. 4, 1986 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-7 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
      - Classrooms, 1987; F-201-3-2-2-8 (Archival box - standard 201-32)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 1, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-9 (Archival box - standard 201-33)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 2, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-10 (Archival box - standard 201-33)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 3, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-11 (Archival box - standard 201-33)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 4, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-12 (Archival box - standard 201-33)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 5, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-13 (Archival box - standard 201-33)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 6, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-14 (Archival box - standard 201-33)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 7, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-15 (Archival box - standard 201-33)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 8, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-16
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 9, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-17
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 10, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-18 (Archival box - standard 201-34)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 11, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-19 (Archival box - standard 201-34)
      - University Space Advisory Committee (USAC), vol. 12, 1988 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-20 (Archival box - standard 201-34)
      - Institute for Molecular Biology buildings, 1989 - 1990; F-201-3-2-2-21 (Archival box - standard 201-34)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.d.
      - West Mall Complex, vol. 1, 1989 - 1994; F-201-3-2-2-22 (Archival box - standard 201-34)
      - West Mall Complex, vol. 2, 1989 - 1994; F-201-3-2-2-23 (Archival box - standard 201-34)
      - West Mall Complex, vol. 3, 1989 - 1994; F-201-3-2-2-24 (Archival box - standard 201-34)
      - West Mall Complex, vol. 4, 1989 - 1994; F-201-3-2-2-25 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
      - Multi-Tenant Facility, 1990 - 1991; F-201-3-2-2-26 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.I.
      - Shrum Classroom Complex, 1990 - 1991; F-201-3-2-2-27 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.g.
      - East Academic Annex, 1991; F-201-3-2-2-28 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.h.
      - South Science Building, 1991 - 1993; F-201-3-2-2-29 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.k.
      - Student Services Building, vol. 1, 1991 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-30 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.j.
      - Student Services Building, vol. 2, 1991 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-31 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
      - Student Services Building, vol. 3, 1991 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-32 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.c.
      - Alcan Facility, 1991 - 1992; F-201-3-2-2-33 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.2.l.
      - Space, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-2-34 (Archival box - standard 201-35)
      - Applied Sciences Building, 1985 - 1992; F-201-3-2-2-35 (Archival box - standard 201-31)
      - Renovations, vol. 3, 1986 - 1996; F-201-3-2-2-36
    - Teaching Support Staff Union (TSSU) consultations, 1991 - 1998; F-201-3-2-3; 11 cm of textual records
      Teaching Support Staff Union
      - TSSU, 1991 - 1998; F-201-3-2-3-1 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
      - TSSU, 1993; F-201-3-2-3-2 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
      - TSSU consultations, 1993 - 1995; F-201-3-2-3-3 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
      - TSSU, vol. 1, 1994; F-201-3-2-3-4 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
      - TSSU, vol. 2, 1994; F-201-3-2-3-5 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
      - TSSU, vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-201-3-2-3-6 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
      - TSSU, vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-201-3-2-3-7 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
    - Simon Fraser University Faculty Association (SFUFA) consultations, 1991 - 1998; F-201-3-2-4; 22 cm of textual records
      Simon Fraser University Faculty Association
      - Librarians, 1991 - 1993; F-201-3-2-4-1 (Archival box - standard 201-36)
      - SFUFA consultations, vol. 1, 1993; F-201-3-2-4-2 (Archival box - standard 201-37)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.13.
      - SFUFA consultations, vol. 2, 1993; F-201-3-2-4-3 (Archival box - standard 201-37)
      - SFUFA - arbitration, 1994; F-201-3-2-4-4 (Archival box - standard 201-37)
      - SFUFA consultations, vol. 1, 1994; F-201-3-2-4-5 (Archival box - standard 201-37)
      - SFUFA consultations, vol. 2, 1994; F-201-3-2-4-6 (Archival box - standard 201-37)
      - SFUFA general - faculty relations, 1994; F-201-3-2-4-7 (Archival box - standard 201-37)
      - SFUFA negotiations, 1994; F-201-3-2-4-8 (Archival box - standard 201-69)
      - SFUFA consultations, vol. 1, 1995; F-201-3-2-4-9 (Archival box - standard 201-37)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.6.
      - SFUFA consultations, vol. 2, 1995; F-201-3-2-4-10 (Archival box - standard 201-38)
      - SFUFA, vol. 1, 1996; F-201-3-2-4-11 (Archival box - standard 201-38)
      - SFUFA, vol. 2, 1996; F-201-3-2-4-12 (Archival box - standard 201-38)
      - SFUFA, 1997 - 1998; F-201-3-2-4-13 (Archival box - standard 201-38)
    - Committee to Review Personal Safety and Security at SFU, 1992 - 1996; F-201-3-2-5; 9 cm of textual records
      Committee to Review Personal Safety and Security at SFU
      - Safety Committee, vol. 1, 1992 - 1994; F-201-3-2-5-1 (Archival box - standard 201-38)
      - Safety Committee, vol. 2, 1992 - 1994; F-201-3-2-5-2 (Archival box - standard 201-38)
        Restricted in part
      - Safety Committee, 1993; F-201-3-2-5-3 (Archival box - standard 201-38)
      - Safety Committee, 1993 - 1994; F-201-3-2-5-4 (Archival box - standard 201-39)
      - Safety Committee, 1993 - 1996; F-201-3-2-5-5 (Archival box - standard 201-39)
    - University computing committees, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-2-6; 12 cm of textual records
      University Computing Advisory Comittee; Committee on Instructional Computing; Academic Computing Services Committee; Committee on Research Computing; Administrative Computing Coordinating Committee
      - University Computing Advisory Committee (UCAC), vol. 1, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-2-6-1 (Archival box - standard 201-39)
      - University Computing Advisory Committee (UCAC), vol. 2, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-2-6-2 (Archival box - standard 201-39)
      - University Computing Advisory Committee (UCAC), vol. 3, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-2-6-3 (Archival box - standard 201-39)
      - University Computing Advisory Committee (UCAC), vol. 4, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-2-6-4 (Archival box - standard 201-39)
      - Committee on Instructional Computing (COIC), 1991 - 1992; F-201-3-2-6-5 (Archival box - standard 201-39)
      - Academic Computing Services Committee (ACSC), 1991 - 1993; F-201-3-2-6-6 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
      - Committee on Research Computing (CORC), 1991 - 1993; F-201-3-2-6-7 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
      - Administrative Computing Coordinating Committee (ACCC), 1991 - 1995; F-201-3-2-6-8 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
    - Legal services, 1991 - 1997; F-201-3-2-7; 17 cm of textual records
      Human Rights Office
      - Legal services, 1991 - 1993; F-201-3-2-7-1 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
        Restricted in whole
      - Legal services, 1991 - 1993; F-201-3-2-7-2 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
      - Legal services, 1991 - 1993; F-201-3-2-7-3 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
      - Harassment case, 1992; F-201-3-2-7-4 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.8.
      - W. Anita Braha, 1992 - 1995; F-201-3-2-7-5 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
        Creator's original file classification code: 3.B.15.
      - Legal services, 1994; F-201-3-2-7-6 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
      - Legal services, 1994 - 1995; F-201-3-2-7-7 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
      - Security, 1996; F-201-3-2-7-8 (Archival box - standard 201-40)
      - Harassment Office, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-7-9 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
      - Harassment Office, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-7-10 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
      - Harassment Office, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-7-11 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
      - Harassment Office, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-7-12 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
      - Harassment Office, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-7-13 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
    - British Columbia Council on Admissions and Transfers (BCCAT), 1992 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8; 23 cm of textual records
      British Columbia Council on Admissions and Transfer
      - BCCAT, 1992; F-201-3-2-8-1 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
      - Transfer Credit Sub-committee, 1992 - 1995; F-201-3-2-8-2 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
      - BCCAT, 1993; F-201-3-2-8-3 (Archival box - standard 201-41)
      - BCCAT, 1994; F-201-3-2-8-4 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, 1995; F-201-3-2-8-5 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, vol. 1, 1996; F-201-3-2-8-6 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, vol. 2, 1996; F-201-3-2-8-7 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, vol. 1, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-8 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, vol. 2, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-9 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, vol. 3, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-10 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, vol. 4, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-11 (Archival box - standard 201-42)
      - BCCAT, vol. 5, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-12 (Archival box - standard 201-43)
      - BCCAT, vol. 6, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-13 (Archival box - standard 201-43)
      - BCCAT, vol. 7, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-14 (Archival box - standard 201-43)
      - BCCAT, vol. 8, 1996 - 1997; F-201-3-2-8-15 (Archival box - standard 201-43)
    - File indices, 1977 - 1994; F-201-3-2-9; 1 cm of textual records
      - File indices, 1977 - 1994; F-201-3-2-9-1 (Archival box - standard 201-43)
  - Academic Advice Centre, 1985 - 1992; F-201-3-3; 13 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's correspondence with, related to, or copied from the Academic Advice Centre. For the whole of its existence (1971-1992), the Centre belonged to the VP Academic's reporting portfolio, though its direct reporting relationship shifted several times between the VP and the AVP. Activities documented in the correspondence include staffing, budget, policy development, and the reorganization and dissolution of the Centre in 1992. Records include correspondence, reports and statistics, student attrition and retention studies, advisors' manuals, and meeting agenda, minutes, and notes.
    Academic Advice Centre
    - Academic Advice Centre, 1985 - 1986; F-201-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-44)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.C.
    - Academic Advice Centre, 1986 - 1987; F-201-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-44)
    - Academic Advice Centre, 1988 - 1989; F-201-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-44)
    - Academic Advice Centre, vol. 1, 1991; F-201-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 201-44)
    - Academic Advice Centre, vol. 2, 1991; F-201-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 201-44)
    - Academic Advice Centre, vol. 3, 1991; F-201-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 201-44)
    - Academic Advice Centre, 1992; F-201-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 201-44)
  - Analytical Studies, 1986 - 1998; F-201-3-4; 14 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's correspondence with, related to, or copied from Analytical Studies. Analytical Studies moved to the VP Academic's reporting portfolio in 1985, although for all of the period covered by this series it reported directly to the VP Academic (rather than the AVP). Records include correspondence, reports, and statistics, including departmental profiles and enrollment statistics.
    Institutional Research and Planning
    - Analytical Studies, 1986; F-201-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.D.2.
    - Analytical Studies, 1987; F-201-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
    - Analytical Studies, 1989; F-201-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.D.
    - Analytical Studies, 1991; F-201-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
    - Analytical Studies, 1992; F-201-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
    - Analytical Studies, 1993; F-201-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
    - Analytical Studies, 1993 - 1994; F-201-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
    - Analytical Studies, 1995; F-201-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 201-45)
    - Analytical Studies, 1996 - 1998; F-201-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 201-47)
  - Cooperative Education, 1985 - 1996; F-201-3-5; 20 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's correspondence with, related to, or copied from Cooperative Education during the period in which it reported to the AVP Academic (1985-1996). After 1996, Cooperative Education reported to Student Services, though it later returned again to the VP Academic portfolio in 1999. Activities documented in the correspondence include departmental budget planning, staffing, program development, and the deliberations and activities of the SFU Coop Advisory Council. Records include correspondence, reports, budgets, program proposals, meeting minutes and supporting papers, and a coop student handbook (1993).
    Cooperative Education; Coop Advisory Council
    - Cooperative Education, vol. 1, 1985 - 1986; F-201-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-47)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.E.
    - Cooperative Education, vol. 2, 1985 - 1986; F-201-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-47)
    - Cooperative Education - budget, 1985 - 1986; F-201-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-47)
    - Cooperative Education, 1985 - 1987; F-201-3-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 201-47)
    - Cooperative Education, 1989; F-201-3-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 201-47)
    - Cooperative Education, 1990 - 1991; F-201-3-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 201-47)
    - Cooperative Education, 1992; F-201-3-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 201-48)
    - Cooperative Education, 1993; F-201-3-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 201-48)
    - Cooperative Education, 1994; F-201-3-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 201-48)
    - Cooperative Education, 1994 - 1995; F-201-3-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 201-48)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.F.
    - Cooperative Education, 1994 - 1996; F-201-3-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 201-43)
  - Financial Aid and Awards, 1985 - 1993; F-201-3-6; 26 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's correspondence with, related to, or copied from the Financial Aid and Awards Office during the period in which it reported to the AVP Academic (1984-1994). Note that until 1989, the Office was called simply the Financial Aid Office. From 1994 it reported to the Registrar, where it was eventually merged with other programs to form part of the Student Academic Resources Office. Activities documented in the correspondence include departmental budget planning, program and policy development, and the external review of the department in 1991. The sub-series also includes one file of correspondence with the Community Relations Office. This appears to have been a short-lived office, established around 1986 with the appointment of Vern Loewen (also Director of Financial Aid) as Community Relations Officer; it does not appear to have continued beyond 1987. Records in the sub-series include correspondence, meeting minutes, budgets, statistics and reports.
    Financial Aid and Awards; Community Relations Office
    - Financial Aid, 1985 - 1986; F-201-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-48)
    - Community Relations, 1986 - 1987; F-201-3-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-48)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.F.a.
    - Financial Aid, vol. 1, 1986 - 1987; F-201-3-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-49)
    - Financial Aid, vol. 2, 1986 - 1987; F-201-3-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 201-49)
    - Financial Aid and Awards, vol. 1, 1989 - 1992; F-201-3-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 201-49)
    - Financial Aid and Awards, vol. 2, 1989 - 1992; F-201-3-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 201-49)
    - Financial Aid and Awards, vol. 1, 1991; F-201-3-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 201-49)
    - Financial Aid and Awards, vol. 2, 1991; F-201-3-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 201-50)
    - Entrance scholarships, 1991 - 1992; F-201-3-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 201-50)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.F.d.
    - Money-related items, 1991 - 1992; F-201-3-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 201-50)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.F.b.
    - Financial Aid and Awards, vol. 1, 1993; F-201-3-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 201-50)
    - Financial Aid and Awards, vol. 2, 1993; F-201-3-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 201-50)
  - Registrar, 1985 - 1996; F-201-3-7; 25 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's correspondence with, related to, or copied from the Registrar's Office during the period in which it reported to the AVP Academic (1985-1996). In 1996, the Registrar's Office was reorganized as part of Student Services. Activities documented in the correspondence include admissions, registration and teleregistration, enrollment management, and IT systems planning. Records include correspondence, reports, surveys, and meeting minutes.
    Registrar's Office
    - Registrar, 1985 - 1986; F-201-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-50)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.G.
    - Registrar, 1986 - 1987; F-201-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-50)
    - Admissions, 1986 - 1987; F-201-3-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.G.2.
    - Registrar - general, 1989 - 1990; F-201-3-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.G.a.
    - Systems development plan, 1990 - 1991; F-201-3-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.G.c.
    - Teleregistration, 1990 - 1992; F-201-3-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.G.d.
    - Admissions, vol. 1, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.G.b.
    - Admissions, vol. 2, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
    - Admissions, vol. 3, 1990 - 1995; F-201-3-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
    - Registrar - general, 1991; F-201-3-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 201-51)
    - Registrar - general, 1991 - 1992; F-201-3-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 201-52)
    - Registrar - general, 1992 - 1993; F-201-3-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 201-52)
    - Registrar - general, vol. 1, 1993 - 1994; F-201-3-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 201-52)
      Creator's original file classification code: 3.E.a.
    - Registrar - general, vol. 2, 1993 - 1994; F-201-3-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 201-52)
    - Registrar, 1995 - 1996; F-201-3-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 201-52)
  - Animal Care Facility, 1990 - 1993; F-201-3-8; 6 cm of textual records